Wade: Hey, Gary.
UNKNOWN: Hi.
Dave: Hey, can you put your characters on Initiative Tracker 3.0?
Gary [?]: 3.0.
Gary: Okay, I want.
Gary: How are you doing?
Dave: Good.
Dave: How are you?
Gary: Atlanta is going okay.
Dave: Good.
Dave: You're going to be there for two weeks?
Gary: I'm in Atlanta for one week and then Bangalore for two weeks.
Dave: Bangalore for two weeks.
Dave: Oh, okay.
Gary: So, unfortunately, I did not write a backstory yet.
Dave: But do you know the backstory?
Dave: I was just going to tell everybody what it was.
Gary: Maybe partially.
Dave: Enough.
Dave: You can be mysterious.
Dave: You can be all shadowhardy.
Gary: Yeah, not shadowhardy.
Gary: No.
Dave: You don't have to tell us all your full backstory.
Dave: Brewberry.
Dave: Good name.
Dave: I like that one.
Gary: We're going to do the consistent plus twos here on initiative.
Dave: That's funny.
Dave: I'll take the alert feet when I can.
Kostadis: Hello, hello.
Kostadis: I need icons.
Dave: I think we put them in the chat for you.
Kostadis: You did?
Dave: I did.
Dave: I did mine last week.
Kostadis: Oh, well, you're better than me.
Dave: Yep, I am.
Kostadis: You're like always better than me.
Kostadis: You are always the best.
Dave: Oh, my gosh.
Dave: This guy.
Dave: I need Wade.
Dave [?]: All right.
Dave: There's Wade.
Dave: Hey, Wade, can you put your character in Initiative Tracker 3.0?
Wade: I believe I can.
Wade: Hold on.
Wade: Let me get everything else set up here.
Wade: Sorry, I'm late.
UNKNOWN: You're right on time.
Kostadis: You're not late because Costatus didn't do his job.
Kostadis [?]: You had a job?
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: I had to get the tokens ready.
Dave: You're making the tokens from our from the image we posted to the chat.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: For future reference, you too can make these with token marker.
Dave: Token maker?
Kostadis: Yeah, token maker.
Dave: Token maker.
Gary: In fact, if you want, it's easier to just make you do it, right?
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave: Exactly.
Kostadis: Plus, it deprives me of an opportunity to futz with your tokens in a way that I find satisfying.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Let me tell everybody my backstory.
Dave: So Vucradin is a.
Kostadis: Are you going to write it down so I have it written down?
Wade [?]: Or do you want us to write them down?
Dave: That's why we have this recorded.
Dave: And have you turned on the AI companion?
Kostadis [?]: Oh, wait.
Kostadis [?]: Hold on.
Kostadis [?]: Let me turn it on.
Dave: Turn on the AI companion and then it will write it for you.
Kostadis: I think I have it by default turned on.
Dave: I don't see the little icon.
Dave [?]: Right.
Dave: Here, ask host.
Dave: There we go.
Dave: Now it's on.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: Yeah.
Dave: Vocraden is a serious musician from what are we doing?
Kostadis [?]: None of that silly music.
UNKNOWN: Neverwinter, Neverwinter.
Dave: Neverwinter from Neverwinter.
Kostadis [?]: Yes.
Dave: And he plays in a piano bar seven days a week and somehow never manages to make any money.
Dave: The patrons don't seem to care very much for the music he plays, but he works very hard.
Dave: And he's broke because he's not making any money from his piano bar despite working very hard.
Dave: So he's going to try adventuring because he's heard that there's a lot of money in it.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave: And he's broke.
Dave: He's done.
Dave: He's very desperate.
Kostadis: He's desperate.
Kostadis: But does he want to be an adventurer?
Kostadis: This is kind of one of those things he's doing.
Dave: No, no, he wants to be a musician.
Dave: He wants to open like, you know, a music studio and play his serious music with other people who are serious with him and not just piano bar patrons.
Dave: But sometimes you got to do the things you have to do.
Kostadis [?]: Sometimes.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So, Gary, this is your drow character.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Wade, do you have a turtle?
Wade: I have a turtle.
Kostadis: Yeah, I saw the very silly turtle image.
Kostadis: Is that the one you want me to use, or do you want me to use something more efficient?
Wade [?]: Fine.
Wade: No, no.
Wade: I played around a bit.
Kostadis: No, I don't care.
Kostadis: It's like, you know, there's a rule of DD that no matter how stupid you make your character, in the end, he always turns serious.
Wade: No, let me let me.
Wade [?]: No, I'm lucky never turned serious.
Wade [?]: Yeah, he did.
Dave: Unlucky became like a caricature.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade: Sorry.
Dave [?]: I'm having things to do.
Wade: I just got to export this.
Wade: Where the heck is PNG?
Kostadis: I think that's the right moment.
Wade: There it is.
Wade: All right.
Wade: Yes.
Wade: Come on.
Wade: I'm sorry.
Wade: I'm not.
Wade: I'm not ready.
Wade: Go on.
Wade: Go on without me for a moment.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So keep telling us about your backstory, man.
Kostadis [?]: Who me or Dave?
Kostadis: Dave, Dave.
Dave: Oh, no, I'm done.
Kostadis [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: Gary, what's your backstory?
Dave: Very simple.
Dave: More will be revealed in time.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Well, I figured.
Kostadis: Gary, your backstory?
Dave: I think we lost, Gary.
Kostadis: Gary.
Dave: What the hell?
Dave: Upside down, cat.
Kostadis [?]: Why is this misbehaving?
Wade [?]: Because it hates you.
Wade: I know.
Wade: I'm just.
Wade: There you go.
Wade: Did that work?
Wade: What the heck is going on here?
Dave [?]: Are you trying to?
Wade: Oh, I have to hit enter.
Wade: I don't know.
Wade: It just looked like it was posting it and then didn't and then stopped.
Dave: Or right arrow.
Dave: Right arrow sometimes works.
Wade: Yeah, it's all right.
Wade: I'm getting there.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Wade: Did we lose Gary?
Dave: Temporarily.
Dave: Oh, wow.
Dave: That's a very, that's a very serious image.
Dave: Wow.
Dave: He looks.
Wade [?]: Oh, I love it.
Dave: Quite peaceful.
Wade [?]: Quite peaceful.
Wade: Yes.
Wade: It's a she.
Wade: It's a lady turtle.
Wade [?]: Oh, I didn't realize that.
UNKNOWN: Very peaceful.
Kostadis: Are you playing a she?
Kostadis: Is that what I'm supposed to infer?
Wade: Yes.
Wade: Okay.
Wade: Is that going to be a problem?
Dave [?]: No, no, no, no.
Dave [?]: No, no.
Dave: Gary has played women several times.
Kostadis: In fact, one time he played two women at the same time.
Kostadis: It was very awkward.
Kostadis: One was a cleric and one was a paladin, and they kept possessing each other's bodies.
Kostadis [?]: Okay, that's a little bizarre.
Dave: Oh, yeah.
Dave: I do faintly remember that.
Wade: What is this like your name?
Dave: Did you have to like roll to see who was successful or something?
Wade [?]: Yes.
Dave [?]: Periodically.
Wade: Oh, we had a split personality.
Wade: That must have been fun to deal with.
Dave: Right.
Dave: It was a split personality.
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Wade [?]: It was awesome.
Dave: An interesting character idea.
Kostadis: It definitely was the most interesting one.
Kostadis: It was one of the more interesting ones.
Kostadis: It didn't quite reach level or Orsic level of excitement, but you know.
Wade: Can I find me?
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Dave [?]: This is the right.
Dave [?]: We want something bright for her.
Wade: I don't remember where to find Spell DC to fill that in.
Dave: So to spells.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade: There's the modifier, the spell attack, and the save DC.
Dave: Yeah, that's it.
Dave [?]: It's right up there.
Wade [?]: That's it to sell save DC.
Dave [?]: Oh, it's a save DC.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Dave: Save DC.
Wade: I was looking right at it.
Wade: I was like, I'm not sure which one to put in.
Wade: Let's see.
Wade: Passive perception.
Wade: Passive investigation.
Wade: I'm kind of blind.
Wade: Passive insight.
Dave: Well, Balfine has 1515.
Dave: Wow.
Dave: Well, we don't have anybody with like three hit points, so that's good.
Wade: Unlucky did fine.
Dave: He somehow managed to make it to the end of the adventure.
Wade: Well, he ended up getting like the stone of soak 100 HP damage or something.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: I mean, I think he got that pretty low by the end.
Kostadis: And plus, he had the most amazing resource ever.
Wade: A cleric?
Wade [?]: Pocket cleric?
Kostadis: Yeah, he had a walking band-aid.
Kostadis: So he didn't actually have 50 hit points.
Kostadis: He had 50 hit points plus whatever the healing maximum of the cleric was.
Kostadis: Right?
Kostadis: That's how it works, right?
Kostadis [?]: That's how it works.
Dave: So we've got a druid, a bard, a barbarian, and a cleric.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Now I have to get your.
Kostadis: I got the tokens.
Kostadis: I need to go do one more thing.
Kostadis: Get your names.
Kostadis: Hey, can you claim your character?
Kostadis: And it's like, I know it doesn't actually matter, but it's kind of one of those.
Wade: You're such a white.
Kostadis [?]: No, I'll do it.
Dave: I did that, right?
Dave [?]: I didn't.
Kostadis [?]: I definitely did not.
Kostadis: It like, I know it doesn't matter, and I know it's not important, but it really is important to me.
Dave: It helps you because you have so many campaigns.
Wade: It's fine.
Wade: I've done.
Wade: I've clicked the camp, whatever.
Wade: I'm going to unassign Vartus.
Wade: Oh, I can't.
Dave [?]: He's deactivated.
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: Well, never mind then.
Wade: Rest in peace, Vartus.
Dave: Neverwinter, huh?
Dave: At some point, I'd like to go to the piano bar and Neverwinter.
Kostadis: We could do that.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: Of course, we could do that.
Dave: That's a ways away, though.
Kostadis: Okay, create a character.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: What's the name of this character?
Kostadis: Balfine Satora.
Kostadis: Hey, we haven't still gotten Gary's version of the story.
Dave: He's going to join in a moment.
Kostadis: By the way, did you like your background?
Dave [?]: Huh?
Dave [?]: I gave you a- Oh, I thought that was that AI-generated, Cassandra?
Wade [?]: No, I actually created it by myself.
Dave: Wow.
Wade: Oh, now I feel bad that I was thinking it was just as an example.
Dave: I just assumed it was AI-generated.
Kostadis: No, no, no.
Wade: No, I mean, I thought it was fun.
UNKNOWN: I just don't want to be attached to nobility or anything.
Wade: I figured you're not attached to nobility.
Wade: She's born, you know, lived out of the house.
Kostadis: She's not attached to no noble.
Wade: No, she's familiar with the noble lifestyle while not being in it.
Kostadis: Yeah, I figured that was the kind of resentment you would like.
Wade: Jeez.
Wade: No, I mean, it's fine.
Kostadis: I just wasn't do whatever you want.
Kostadis: I gave you some input.
Kostadis: Like, give us a background.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Dave: Gary.
Kostadis [?]: Hi.
Gary [?]: Sorry.
Kostadis: I have to do two more.
Dave: Gary, do you have any backstory to share?
Gary [?]: Not really.
Gary [?]: I'm so disappointed.
Gary [?]: I know.
Kostadis: You should be disappointed.
Kostadis: And this is very unfortunate.
Kostadis: We will have to resort to background by screenwriters over time.
Dave: Or roll.
Dave: Roll for background.
Wade: It's a pleasure to meet you.
Dave: Exactly.
Dave: Plus one mace.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Gary: So, you know, we have a Drew, a drow cleric of, I think I said Lathander, didn't I?
Dave [?]: Yes.
Dave: Very good drone cleric.
Kostadis: No, she's embracing.
Kostadis: She's embracing herself.
Dave: She's embracing the light.
Gary: She's masochistic.
Gary: She likes pain.
Gary: And so, okay.
Dave: Has she developed a tolerance to the light?
Kostadis [?]: No, no, she likes it.
Kostadis [?]: Wow.
Kostadis [?]: If only she had a shell she could retreat into.
Dave: Like a permanent disadvantage, huh?
Kostadis: No, no, they don't have disadvantage anymore in fifth edition.
Kostadis: They don't, do they?
Kostadis: I don't think so.
Kostadis: No, they don't.
Kostadis: Yeah, they don't.
Gary: Yeah.
Gary: So that's at least Balfine right now.
Gary: And then Brewberry, I don't know that I have a background for him either, but he's, you know, like the Goliath Uthgart barbarian.
Gary: And I don't know that I fully figured out like how he's there with the Uthgart.
Kostadis: Well, it's close by, physically.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: Yeah. He could, I mean, depending on where he, I mean, so the real question is, did how did Balfine and the Barbarian meet?
Gary: Oh, should are we assuming that they met first?
Gary [?]: How did you all beat?
Gary [?]: Or you all show up in Phandalin, you know, traveling.
Dave: I'm following this like get rich quick flyer that was posted in Neverwinter.
Wade: Oh, see, my plan for backstory was to have her running as a guide.
Wade: She could be leading people back into town or whatever, at least to get her at the party.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: That seems like a perfect setup for the musician and the turtle.
Wade: Yes.
Wade: In her sunset year, she's just leading tours around the forest, guiding adventurers to other places.
Kostadis: Right.
Kostadis: You know, you don't know where you don't adventure, right?
Kostadis: You're a bard.
Kostadis: You're a musician.
Kostadis: You're too good for this life.
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Dave: I'm slumming it.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: And when she offers to give you a tour, you say yes.
Kostadis: And when she asks to be paid, you say there's this thing called adventuring.
Wade: I'll pay you in a song.
Wade: Oh, great.
Dave: Wait, I have to pay her?
Dave: I thought I got paid.
Dave: The flyer said I would be paid.
Gary: I think Brewberry.
Dave: I don't have any money.
Gary [?]: Oh, dear.
Gary [?]: You'll have to work it off.
Gary: I think Brewberry, when he was, let's go with kicked out of the Uthgart Barbarian.
Dave: He's kicked out.
Dave: Okay.
Gary: I think for being a drunk, I think we might go with that.
Dave [?]: Hey, it's Uncle June.
Dave: Yeah, Uncle June.
Gary: Maybe not that bad.
Gary: A little bit of a let's go with a dopey giant sort of character.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: Does the Asimar have a light night vision?
Kostadis [?]: Drowl?
UNKNOWN: No, no, I'm talking about the Asimar.
Dave [?]: Vukradin.
Dave: Asimar has, yeah, it has dark vision, yes.
Kostadis: What's the range of it?
Gary: We want to put this on the tracker.
Gary [?]: No, no, I need it for putting it in.
Dave: 60 feet.
Dave: All right.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Gary [?]: All right.
Gary [?]: Okay, keep going.
Gary: And then so he got kicked out of the Uthgardt for being too much of a drunk.
Gary: And then, you know, like as he stumbled into town, he just wanted some friends.
Gary: And then the flyer offered, you know, like someone to hang out with.
Gary: So with that as a motivation.
Dave: Casual.
Dave: Sure, let's go around the forest together.
Dave: That'll be fun.
Gary: It was lonely.
Gary: I needed someone to hang out with.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: I can play you a song.
Dave: Do you like songs?
Kostadis: I do.
Dave: Oh, perfect.
Kostadis: Hey, does I don't think turtles have night vision, right?
Kostadis: Wade, do turtles have night vision?
Wade: I'm muted.
Wade: I'm saying I don't believe they do.
Dave: So go to features and traits.
Wade: I don't see it anywhere in the usual.
UNKNOWN: Yeah, no, it's fine.
Dave [?]: She doesn't need it.
Wade [?]: Excellent.
UNKNOWN: I have a light spell, so we can just cast light.
UNKNOWN: Light Cantrip.
Wade [?]: We can just cast light whenever we need it.
Wade: We can just roll in a shell and tumble down the hill like a boulder.
Gary: My drow cleric would love to cast light spells for me.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis [?]: It hurts myself.
Kostadis: I just want to say that your cleric is very conflicted about her role in life.
Gary: I think she's not conflicted at all.
Gary: But how she got here and how she found this particular path that is something that will need some thought.
Kostadis: Okay, but does she know the barbarian?
Kostadis: Does she meet the barbarian, or is the barbarian picked up from Neverwinter from a bar, the same piano bar that Dave was that Vukradin?
Kostadis: Like, you know, the barbarian was a drunk in the bar.
Kostadis: He was being kicked out because he didn't pay his bills.
Kostadis: Vukradin made a claim that, you know, I know where we can make money.
UNKNOWN: I've got his paper.
Gary: I think he probably showed up at the bar lonely and then looking for someone to drink with.
Gary [?]: All right.
Gary [?]: Okay.
Dave: I drink at the bar.
Dave: I play piano.
Gary: Oh.
Gary: I drink tea.
Dave: Yeah.
Dave: Follow tales only.
Kostadis: Like maybe.
Kostadis: Oh, wait.
Kostadis: Let me give you another.
Kostadis: The barbarian actually finds the music that Vukradin to be amazing.
Dave: It is amazing.
Kostadis: No, no, no.
Kostadis: Like, like, he, it's like, for him, this is like the music of the ages.
Kostadis [?]: Let's say he grew up with Uthgardt music, which is just drums.
Gary: And like, all these pitches and tones are like amazing.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: I mean, it's like he's just, you know, so like he's like your biggest fan.
Kostadis [?]: There we go.
Kostadis: That's not just your biggest fan, but he also gets really offended when other people don't share in the enthusiastic appraisal of your music.
Dave: Me too.
Dave [?]: Yeah, I'm just, yeah.
Kostadis: Yes, let's go with that.
Kostadis [?]: That's good.
Dave: Well, that's nice of you guys.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: I just want to make sure we're all okay with that.
Kostadis: No issues.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: Dave?
Dave: Sure.
Dave [?]: Did that work?
Kostadis: What?
Dave: Make that work?
Kostadis: I mean, he doesn't have to always like it.
Kostadis: He could at some point decide that, you know, the music sucks.
Dave: Well, I don't have a piano with me.
Dave: So I'm going to have to fall back to like flute and clarinet in camp.
Wade [?]: That's fine. All right. Teach me the drums. I'm not a percussionist. Maybe the barbarian can help you with that. No. Percussion is really boring.
Wade: It makes the song.
Gary: And too much of that.
Gary: And it makes my head pound after drinking.
Wade: The drinking is what makes your head pound.
Gary [?]: Okay.
Gary [?]: The total perfect.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis: I think it's a look.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: Download.
Kostadis: Okie dokie.
Kostadis: And then all right.
Kostadis: So it.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: Next thing I need to do is I need to invite you to this adventure.
Dave: Yes.
Dave: I'm rolling.
Dave: You could delete some of these.
Dave: You could delete old and be one guys.
Kostadis: I don't delete them, but I can archive them.
Wade: There's no sense in deleting anything with cloud storage.
Wade: It's infinite.
Wade [?]: Yes, exactly.
Dave: Amazing.
Dave: We've created an infinite storage.
Dave [?]: Somebody else is paying for it.
UNKNOWN: It's infinite to me.
Wade: What are you up to, idiot?
Wade: All right.
Wade: Sorry.
Wade: I don't put that in the middle.
Dave [?]: What do you cat doing?
Dave: We don't see very much.
Wade: You won't see her in here, not with the dog around.
Wade: They have lots of roll 20 link in the chat.
Wade: Now I got to find which of these seven chats.
Wade [?]: All right, there it is.
Wade [?]: Google chat.
Dave [?]: Yeah.
Wade: Ice Spire.
Wade [?]: What?
Gary: I don't have to accept this invitation.
Kostadis: You just have to click on that link and do whatever it says.
Kostadis: I don't actually know what it says.
Dave: Why am I so much smaller than everybody else?
Kostadis: You're not smaller than everybody else.
Kostadis [?]: You are?
Dave [?]: No, he is.
Dave: I'm definitely smaller.
Kostadis [?]: He is definitely smaller.
Kostadis: Well, because I felt that if I didn't have your musical instrument, it would be somehow demeaning.
Kostadis: I could create a new image.
Dave: It's fine.
Dave: I can be small.
Kostadis: I mean, I hate to say this, but visual.
Dave [?]: Let me just say back.
UNKNOWN: Visual arts was never your thing.
Dave: No.
Kostadis [?]: Right.
Kostadis: And so this was the best.
Dave: But I have a great appreciation for all the arts.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: Well, I thought.
Dave: It wasn't my thing.
Dave: This wasn't, you know, not something I was tanned to at.
Kostadis: Okay.
Wade: Why can't I get rid of this turn order thing?
Wade [?]: What turn order thing?
Wade: I don't know.
Wade: That little turn order thing on roll 20.
Dave: Oh, yeah.
Dave: I hate that thing.
Wade [?]: Oh, that's because I have to click on it.
Dave [?]: Oh, you have to delete it.
Dave [?]: Okay, I was wondering.
Dave: You can shrink it a little bit and then put it in the corner.
Wade: I've never seen it before.
Wade: Now, you know, it's all I see.
Wade [?]: Oh, wow.
Kostadis: Okay.
Wade [?]: Launch game.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Gary, Wade, Dave, we have all joined.
Dave: Alrighty.
Kostadis: All righty.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: Establishment calming down.
Gary: So do so.
Gary: So what does this flyer set again?
Gary: The flyers hang around.
Dave: It said, come to Phandalin.
Gary [?]: Phandalin?
Dave: Phandalin?
Dave: Is that where we are?
Gary [?]: Phandalin.
Kostadis: Phandalin.
Dave: Phandalin.
Kostadis [?]: I don't know.
UNKNOWN: I just followed Brewbeary.
Dave: It said, come here and easy money shall be yours.
Kostadis: What it said, what it said was: with the end of the War of the Giants and the War of the Dragons, the hinterland of Neverwinter is in need of adventurers and heroes to bring peace and prosperity.
UNKNOWN: No, no, that's not right.
UNKNOWN: It definitely said something about money.
Dave: I mean, I'm all for peace and prosperity.
Dave: I totally believe in that.
Dave: But at this point, I'm having trouble buying food to eat.
Kostadis: No, no, I'm sorry.
Kostadis: So it's like, are you adventures, heroes, people who want to make a change?
Kostadis: The kingdom, Neverwinter needs you.
Dave: Phandalin.
Kostadis: No, Phandalin.
Dave [?]: Neverwinter needs you.
Kostadis: Phandalin happens to be an ally as part of the hinterland of Neverwinter.
Kostadis: And Lord Neverember wants you to go help him secure the territories.
Dave: Was he literally named Lord Neverember?
Kostadis: Yeah, Neverember.
Kostadis: I did not come up with a eunuch.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Dave: And a Gygax special Neverember?
Kostadis: Dude, I did not come up with it.
Kostadis [?]: Wow.
Dave [?]: No, it was not invented by Gygax.
Kostadis [?]: Sounds like we needed a new mayor.
Dave: We'll take care of that in a future adventure, yes.
Kostadis [?]: Is Wallace still around?
Dave: We're going to need a better name for sure.
Kostadis: Yeah, Wallace is not only around, he's got kids now.
Dave: That's right.
Kostadis [?]: Don't we all?
UNKNOWN: Orsik's hanging out with him, taking care of the kids.
Gary [?]: Yeah, it's, you know, yeah.
Gary: I'm having a little trouble hooking Valfin here.
Gary: So I don't think she sees herself as a hero.
Kostadis: Okay.
Gary: The lure of like maybe learning the hardships of traveling on the road, like that, that might be something.
Gary [?]: She's not the hero type, right?
Gary: Why is this going to be a bad experience for her?
Gary: Like, that's what she needs to know.
Kostadis: It doesn't have to be a bad experience.
Kostadis: There's nothing about this that says it has to be bad.
Gary: Well, I mean, this is her motivation is like inflicting pain on herself.
Kostadis: Oh, on that's going to be a weird one for my girl.
Dave: That's going to be a weird one.
Dave: Did not see that.
Kostadis [?]: She's not going to want to see your girl suffer.
Kostadis: But is it suffering if it's something you want to happen to yourself?
Wade: If you want it, then it's not suffering.
Kostadis: Okay, then you and her can have a wonderfully long and complex conversation.
Gary [?]: All right.
Kostadis: But, you know, like that's part of the Lathander and Drow combo. There we go. Okay. So let's see. Okay. All righty. Okay. So hold on. Let me just do one more thing. That should not be here. There we go. All right. So.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So, yes.
Kostadis: So what the.
Kostadis: Let me do as I say.
Kostadis: So.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So hold on.
Kostadis: There's just one more thing I need to do, which is open 12.
Kostadis: This is the.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Can you guys see your player token?
Wade: I can see a box of four player tokens.
Kostadis: Yes, great.
Kostadis: So that is my new convention for.
Kostadis: I don't know whether I did it with my last campaign.
Wade: You didn't do it with us last time.
Kostadis [?]: Just do us as individuals.
Kostadis: Yeah, so I discovered this.
Kostadis: This is a much easier way of having all four of you on the map.
Wade [?]: All right.
Wade: I mean, you could just say like party and have like a little party balloon or something.
Dave: Yeah, but this is prettier.
Wade: It is.
Wade: I can see that I'm in the bottom right as I belong.
Dave: What's the symbolism of the bottom right?
Kostadis: Yeah, you got me worried there, man.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So, okay.
Kostadis: So just to remind you, so Neverwinter managed to survive the storm known as the War of the Dragons.
Kostadis: It managed to survive the storm known as the War of the Giants.
Kostadis: And now, after several managed to survive the barbarian hordes that made it.
Dave: Is that what's been going on?
Dave: For like the last five years, that's been happening?
Dave: I missed all of that.
Wade [?]: Yes, yes.
Kostadis [?]: The land has been crying out.
UNKNOWN: Right.
Kostadis: Neverwinter had, you know, Neverwinter was strategically placed sufficiently far away from the hordes of the Uthgardtian barbarians that after the War of the Giants ended, was able to avoid the worst of the tribal wars.
Gary: Yeah, the barbarians.
Gary: Yeah, that was.
Kostadis: But now, now, now, what is it?
Kostadis: Now, Neverwinter is all about growth, advancing, making things better.
Kostadis: And, you know, after having had some trouble to the north with its hinterland, it's proposing to re-establish trade and outposts to the south.
Kostadis: And one of those is Phandalin.
Kostadis: Phandalin has been having trouble.
Kostadis: And because Lord Neverember, well, there's limited budget, limited limited member, limited resources.
Kostadis: And, you know, he's come up with a brilliant scheme, hiring adventures.
Kostadis: For those of you in the management biz, he's going with contractors because they have fewer benefits.
Gary: That's our thing.
Kostadis: And as his convention, anybody who does a good turn for the kingdom can keep whatever the gold and treasure they want, etc.
Kostadis: Well, if you ever had enough money for taxes, that's what he meant.
Dave: Oh, no, it's tax-free income, is what you're telling me.
Wade [?]: Yes, it's tax-free.
Wade: Well, that's not typical for $10.99.
Dave: Okay, well.
Kostadis: So the paper.
Kostadis: Yeah, so the paper is calling all adventurers to head south, to go clear the hinterland of monsters, enemies of Neverwinter, and re-establish civilization and the march of progress.
Dave: And after we clear a monster, then what do we do?
Wade: Do you bring their scalps?
Wade: Seems vile.
Dave: Do we take them to Lord Neverember?
Kostadis: No, no, no.
Wade: Like a cat delivering a dead mouse.
Kostadis: Well, so I'm going to assume that you're.
Kostadis: I'm going to assume that as you pick up this notice, a guard is standing next, a guard is standing next to you in Neverwinter and says, looks at you with this quirky expression and says, no, please, for the love of goodness, all that is good, do not bring anything to his lordship.
Kostadis: Why do you ask?
Kostadis: Are you asking about how you make the money?
Dave: Yes.
Kostadis: He pauses and goes, well, I am, of course, an official city guard and get paid on a regular basis, have benefits.
Dave: So, like that.
Kostadis: I'm off.
Kostadis: That is not how adventures get paid.
Kostadis: You are an adventurer, or at least this is what we're looking to hire.
Kostadis: And the way they make money is by defeating the monsters and securing whatever trinkets and treasure they might have amongst their goods.
Wade [?]: So we just loot them.
Dave: You just take the money from the monsters?
Dave: Yes.
Kostadis: It's an excellent system.
Kostadis: We get what we want.
Dave: Where did the monsters get that money from?
Kostadis: I don't know.
Kostadis: And to be quite honest with you, Lord Neverember and the guard don't care.
Dave: Yeah, but I care.
Kostadis: You aren't going to be very wealthy in this adventuring business if you care too much about these details.
Dave: Well, now, I'm not super dumb.
Dave: I mean, I can imagine the monsters got the money from killing people.
Dave: Yes.
Dave: And so, rightfully, that money belongs to their heirs.
Dave [?]: Yes.
Dave: So we'll be returning the money to their heirs.
Kostadis: If you wish to remain.
Kostadis: Yes, but the guard says, You, sir, are you sure you're not a paladin?
Kostadis: A paladin.
Dave: I'm just very confused about why we would be trafficking in stolen goods.
Dave: Aren't you a guard?
Kostadis: He pauses.
Kostadis: You are absolutely correct.
Kostadis: However, we view it in a different way.
Kostadis: Outside of the civilized boundaries of Neverwinter's walls, the laws of the laws of Neverwinter do not apply.
Kostadis: And that is why we need you to go and establish civilization to pacify the areas so that the laws can be done.
Dave: And once the civilization is established, we should follow those laws.
Kostadis: Yes, but until then, we are in the law of the hinterland.
Dave: This seems like very grayish to me.
Kostadis: He points to the city wall.
Dave [?]: The gray begins at the wall.
Kostadis [?]: I think we should return the money to the rightful owners.
Kostadis: The guardsman's eyes sparkle and says, I have an even better idea.
Kostadis: The city guard has a retirement fund.
Dave: Well, I know.
Dave: I mean, if we can't establish who the rightful owners are.
Kostadis: No, no, no, no.
Kostadis: I'm not saying that.
Kostadis: I'm not saying you should donate it to the city guard retirement fund, where we promise to look aggressively for anyone who might claim this treasure.
Kostadis: And only if after a suitable amount of time would it fall into the city retirement fund.
Kostadis: This way, you would know that the money was being guarded and that people would know where to go look for it.
Dave: Well, I'll think about that.
Kostadis: I just want you to know that is the if you're concerned.
Kostadis: I understand your concerns, and that is why I'm very concerned about this.
Dave: The city guards.
Dave: You've signed up to be trafficking in stolen goods.
Wade: You haven't signed up for anything yet, have you?
Dave: Well, I'm desperate.
Dave: I came to Phandalin for this.
Kostadis: Oh, no, yeah, this is as you haven't left Neverwinter.
Kostadis: Now, so now you've leave.
Kostadis: Yeah, I'm just saying.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: So you arrive.
Kostadis: So along the way, Brewbeary, you know, is really excited about your musical style, has decided to follow you.
Kostadis: So, you know, you've acquired him as a traveling companion.
Kostadis: He's very talkative.
Kostadis: Not.
Dave: Is he not talkative?
Gary [?]: Is he talkative?
UNKNOWN: With notes.
Dave: What's that?
Gary: Love music with notes.
Gary [?]: Does Brewbeary periodically try to sing?
Kostadis [?]: I agree, Brewbeary.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: And less talking, more music.
Kostadis: And along the way, you guys encounter.
Kostadis: So how does this drow show up in all of this?
Kostadis [?]: I'm not quite sure yet.
Gary: So, you know, like she grew up in the Drow cities somewhere.
Gary: I don't know.
Kostadis: Okay, so since you said that, something has happened in the underdark over the last year or so, where the city of the main city of the Drow was completely pulverized by demons that ran wild.
Gary: Well, you know, like that tends to happen.
Wade: This wasn't Bob Saget, was it?
Kostadis: No, no, it was not Bob Saget.
UNKNOWN: I mean, so she could be, you know, that could be what inspired her to become a cleric of the light as she saw the devastation that was brought by worshiping the evil clerics of Lolth and so on and so forth and demonic powers.
UNKNOWN: And, you know, she's had a massive change of heart.
Kostadis [?]: Change of heart.
Gary: Yeah, I'm not sure that's entirely the thing.
Gary: Like, I'm not going to go through.
Kostadis: Or maybe she's unimpressed with their power that they let their chosen people die off in that spectacular way and didn't raise a finger.
Kostadis [?]: It could just be driven out.
Kostadis: Okay, driven out.
Gary: Yeah, so like maybe she grew up in the dark and then got an exposure to sunlight, having been forced out of the city, and was like, wow, this is great.
Gary: Lathander, though.
Kostadis: Well, so, you know, if she shows up in Neverwinter, there's likely a temple of Lathander around there.
Gary: Yeah, she's like enthralled by the sunlight that's going on and then ends up in Neverwinter, and then there's like a temple of the sun.
UNKNOWN: Oh, my goodness.
Kostadis: Right.
Kostadis: And, you know, the clerics of Lathander are like ecstatic to have this like Drow want to be one of them because it's kind of like proves the righteousness of their god that even the drow would worship.
Gary: Sure, yeah.
Gary: All right.
Kostadis: If that worked for them, I'm just telling you why they would be excited by this.
Kostadis: Like all religious cults, they have their opinions.
UNKNOWN: Okay, so like her first exposure to the sun is a very religious experience.
Kostadis: Yes, yes.
Gary: She's bored by it and then you know, wanders into town and then keeps going with us.
Gary: Yeah.
Kostadis: Right.
Kostadis: And, you know, since she's interested in paint, but you know, Neverwinter is too civilized.
Kostadis [?]: Too civilized.
Kostadis: Well, she is a drow.
Kostadis: There's no assassinations going on.
Kostadis: There's no torture racks.
Kostadis: There's, you know, there's no open-air slave markets.
Kostadis: There's no conspiracies to destroy other noble houses.
Kostadis: It's all very boring.
Kostadis: So when she sees the flyer, she decides that this would be more painful.
Gary: Yeah, okay.
Gary: There we go.
Gary: That's a motivation.
Kostadis: She's like, you know, this is just boring.
Kostadis: Yes, boring.
Kostadis: Right.
Kostadis: And she's learned from hanging out amongst the upper world that people don't take kindly when you rob or kill or torture people at random.
Dave: I've got to spend money from monsters in this place, though.
Kostadis: Yes, which the drow is totally cool with.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah, yeah, I think we're good with that.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Does the drow know anything about the music player?
Kostadis [?]: Music?
Kostadis: No, no, like about like, is Varoujan's music something that the Drow knows about?
Kostadis: Or is she like, you know, is he so obscure?
Dave [?]: I don't know why she would care about music.
Kostadis: Exactly.
Dave [?]: I'm just saying she would never have heard of his music.
UNKNOWN: That's what I'm asking.
Dave: That's fine.
Gary: I don't think she's necessarily a luck.
Gary: So that doesn't work out.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So that's fine.
Kostadis: She could also have a dim view of music played by Aasimar.
Dave: Did you know that back at the piano bar, we used to survey the patrons on what they thought of the music?
Gary: Aasimar is good.
Gary: Yes.
Dave [?]: That's right.
Gary: Or celestial.
Gary: Sorry.
Gary: That would be something she hasn't seen much of.
Gary: And, you know, it's close to a connection to the sun.
Gary: Yeah.
Gary: Sunlight does he appear.
Gary [?]: Okay.
Gary [?]: That's good.
Gary: All right.
Gary: Is she shiny?
Dave: Anyway, I was going to say Brewbeary is the only patron who ever gave me a 10 out of 10 on the survey.
Gary: I think he did.
Gary: Yes.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So you guys should be seeing the sword coast map.
Kostadis: Yes.
UNKNOWN: Yes.
UNKNOWN: I think I have.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Let me just do a few more things.
Kostadis: There's a couple more locations that I need to make visible.
Kostadis: Right.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So, and you are arriving in Phandalin.
Kostadis: All right.
Gary [?]: Where is it?
Gary: So this is an uneventful trip along the high road.
Kostadis: Yes, yes.
Kostadis: This is, you know, the adventure begins in Phandalin.
Gary [?]: All right.
Gary: Are we like does like the city guards send out like troops and then maybe we accompany them like part way and then yes or you're a merchant or something like that.
Kostadis: Merchant caravan after the after the War of the Dragon and the War of the Giants, the the road, the Triboar, the high road has become better patrolled and better guarded.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So you arrive.
Wade: So we do.
Kostadis: Yes, you do.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Let me see.
Kostadis: What am I looking at?
Wade [?]: All right.
Wade: A quaint little town.
Wade [?]: A great little town.
Wade [?]: Little town.
Wade: Doesn't even have a wall, does it?
Dave [?]: It's a silent village.
Wade: Actually, kind of weird.
Wade: There's like no natural defense.
Wade: There's no water riffer, nothing like that.
Dave: It's like there was a city wall, but it's been lost to the ages.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So let me just go back to this guy.
Dave: Okay.
Wade [?]: Hold on.
Wade [?]: Got it.
Wade: Hold on.
Wade: That's just me goofing around.
Dave: Oh, okay.
Wade: Pink is me, because Thaddus is blue.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: There we go to.
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: Let me just go back to the right locations.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So you arrive in Phandalin.
Kostadis: And right here, you're coming in from Triboar, which I'll make you a little bit bigger so that we can see it.
Kostadis: And as you pass by, you see a bunch of locations.
Kostadis: Let me just.
Kostadis: There's actually something I'm supposed to read.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: When nestled in the rocky foothills of the snow-capped mountains, of the snow-capped Sword Mountains, is the mining town of Phandalin, which consists of 40 or 50 simple log buildings.
Kostadis: Crumbling stone ruins surround the newer houses and shop, showing how this must have been a much larger town in centuries past.
Kostadis: Phandalin's residents are quiet, hard-working folk who came from distant cities to eke out a life amid the harsh wilderness.
Kostadis: They are farmers, stonecutters, blacksmiths, traders, prospectors, and children.
Kostadis: The town has no walls and no garrison.
Kostadis: Most of the adults keep weapons within easy reach in case the need for arms should arise.
Kostadis: Visitors are welcome here, especially if they have coin to spend or news to share.
Kostadis: The Stonehill Inn at the center of the town offers modest meals.
Kostadis: A couple of doors from the inn posted outside.
Kostadis: The Townmaster's Hall is a job for adventurers.
Kostadis: So, I presume you go to the Townmaster's Hall.
Wade: How long have we been walking?
Kostadis: I'm assuming you've been walking for several days.
Kostadis: It's kind of like early in the morning.
Kostadis: Like, it's up to you.
Wade: You know, meals sounds a little better than just running straight to work.
Dave [?]: All right.
Wade [?]: To the inn.
Wade [?]: Are the meals free?
Wade: Huh?
Dave: Are the meals free?
Wade: Where have you been living that meals are free?
Dave: Well, I don't have any money for the meal.
Dave: I'll just eat my rations outside.
Dave: You guys go ahead.
Wade: Starving artists.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So these are, as you're walking by, you see these stores on the left and the right of the road.
Kostadis: And you, as you, and across the street, you see a Lionshield Coster.
Kostadis: The famous interdimensional store where one used to be able to buy everything.
Kostadis: But apparently, rumor has it that their supply chain has been disrupted.
Wade: Damn COVID.
Wade [?]: Terrifying.
Wade [?]: What?
Dave: Tariffs.
Wade: Oh, tariffs, yeah.
Wade [?]: Sorry, I'm not up to date on my memes.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So you want to go to the Stonehill Inn.
Kostadis: Is that what I heard?
Wade: I mean, I feel like after traveling for a day, it's just getting off our feet for a while sounds better than getting a negotiation.
Wade: But if the bard has, you know, his drawers, we won't.
Dave: Maybe I could play for my meal.
Wade: You could sit outside and play and see if you can, you know, upturn your hat or whatever.
Dave: Maybe people drop some coin performance for money.
Dave: Yeah, I would do that.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So the Stonehill Inn was a modest two-story roadhouse.
Kostadis: It has several rooms for rent on the upper floor.
Kostadis: And the proprietor is a short, friendly male human named Toblin Stonehill.
Kostadis: Toblin is very glad to see you.
Dave [?]: Business is hard for him.
Dave: Does he know it?
Kostadis: No, he's very glad to see you.
Kostadis: Your business.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: Right?
Kostadis: He says hello to you, walks up to a table, starts cleaning it, and says, please sit.
Kostadis: Rest your weary legs.
Kostadis: How can I help you?
Wade: Absolutely.
Wade: Tea.
Wade [?]: Tea?
Kostadis: Tea?
Kostadis: Just tea?
Kostadis [?]: Just tea.
Kostadis: You want me to boil water and give it to you?
Kostadis [?]: Yes.
Wade: I have the herbs myself if you don't.
Kostadis: He looks at you, and you're somewhat of a large creature, and he looks at his chair.
Wade: Oh, we're getting to the fat shaving now.
Kostadis: He says, I think you should sit right here, but if you don't mind, I'd like to get the sturdier chair.
Kostadis: He comes back.
Kostadis: He comes back with a sturdier chair.
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: He says, well, that will be 10 copper pieces for the boiled water.
Kostadis [?]: I assume I have some amount of starting.
Dave: I want to play for your inn for a while.
Dave: I have no money.
Dave: I got a 17 on my performance roll.
UNKNOWN: I'm very good, actually.
Kostadis: He pauses and says, well, if you have something, one of the more fashionable tunes from Waterdeep or from Neverwinter, I think, or even Tribor.
Dave: Yes, yes, one of those.
Kostadis: Yeah, I'd be delighted to hear that.
Kostadis [?]: Of course, that's what those bangers here play Freebird.
Dave: Yeah, totally.
Dave: Freebird.
Kostadis: He seems upset.
Dave [?]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
UNKNOWN: I'll play whatever you want.
UNKNOWN: Whatever you want.
Kostadis: He goes, Toblin is a little bit upset.
Kostadis: He goes, I didn't realize that.
Kostadis: My music, if you have some.
Dave: I'm here to please.
Kostadis: I'm desperate.
Kostadis: He goes, well, I mean, if you're willing to have one of my creations, I think I could be even entertained by one of yours.
Kostadis [?]: What are your creations?
Kostadis: You seem to want to play a music piece of your own.
Dave: Well, okay.
Dave: So I can spend the evening playing music.
Dave: And I don't know if he has a piano, but I have a couple instruments.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: Roll your performance to see how well he is.
Dave: I got a 17.
Kostadis: He is very impressed with your music.
Kostadis: He's very delighted.
Kostadis: As you're playing the music, he goes, Well, that is definitely worth some ale.
Kostadis: And he pours you a glass of beer and hands it to you.
Dave: But did you love it?
Kostadis: He smiles and roll your perception.
Kostadis: What's your perception?
Dave: I got a 15 on my perception roll.
Kostadis: All right, now roll your insight or investigation, whichever one's higher.
Dave: Four.
Kostadis: Okay, you definitely are not sure whether he's telling the truth.
Dave: Well, if you didn't love it, I can't take your beer.
Gary: With a four, you probably believe him.
Gary [?]: Yeah, actually, no, that's true.
UNKNOWN: With a four, you believe him.
Dave: I believe it.
Dave: All right.
Kostadis [?]: Well, then I believe it.
Kostadis: Well, yeah, you did not perceive the lie, right?
Kostadis: Right, yeah.
Kostadis: So, yes.
Kostadis: No, let me try this differently.
Kostadis: You got the impression that he adored your music.
Dave: All right.
Dave: Well, then I will take the beer.
Dave [?]: Right.
Kostadis [?]: Sometimes it's good to be an idiot.
Kostadis: Bramgrim.
Kostadis: Here's his bless.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Dave: So Bramgrim liked it.
Dave: He's my number one fan.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So he apparently I'm supposed to reveal a story here.
Kostadis [?]: Excellent.
Gary: And I think Felkur was bored with all this display of music.
Gary [?]: All right.
Gary: We'll say she's not a music lover.
Kostadis: She goes, once again, the orcs have come down from the mountains to prey on the lowlands.
Kostadis: If Neverwinter doesn't send help soon, the orcs will overrun Phandalin and destroy everything we work so hard to rebuild.
Kostadis: Pauses.
Kostadis: Do you have anything to do with Phandalin?
Kostadis: Like, are you part of the support Neverwinter is sending to us?
Kostadis [?]: Yeah, that's right.
Dave [?]: If there's money in it.
Kostadis: Well, I.
Kostadis: Ah, money?
Kostadis: I thought Neverwinter was going to pay you, not us.
Kostadis: Oh, your adventures.
Kostadis [?]: What gave it away?
Dave: I don't really understand how we're going to get paid.
Kostadis: Well, that's very easy, he says.
Kostadis: Outside the Townmaster's Hall, there is a quest board.
Kostadis: The Townmaster, the city has some problems, and it's best if you go there and check them out.
Dave: Okay.
Kostadis [?]: Are you dealing with these orcs on that list?
Kostadis: Well, you'd have to go check what the townmaster has decided is important enough for the city to collect.
Kostadis: He is, in my mind, I'm not sure how he prioritizes things.
Wade: Do you know why the orcs are causing trouble lately?
Kostadis: Well, you must have heard of the War of the Dragons and the War of the Giants, followed by the barbarian hordes, followed by the disturbances in the Underdark.
Wade: Oh, the world is always at war.
Wade: What's special about these orcs today?
Kostadis: Well, usually during these orcs like to expand, and when there isn't a strong army to hold them back, they expand into territories that don't belong to them.
Wade: So, wait, was there a strong army here previously that disbanded?
Kostadis: Well, the various wars depleted Neverwinter's resources.
Wade [?]: And so.
Kostadis [?]: This place doesn't look like it ever held a lot of troops in the past, I don't know, 200 years.
Kostadis: No, no, no.
Kostadis: Phandalin has never been a place with a large army.
Kostadis: It was overrun by orcs many years ago, but since then it's recovered.
Kostadis: I, in fact, lived in Tribor and managed to get word about the disaster that came there from the Uthgaritian barbarians.
Kostadis: He looks at you.
Kostadis: You wouldn't be one of those barbarians, would you?
Kostadis: I'm so sorry.
Wade: Are you apologizing for your ancestors?
Dave: I can vouch for him.
Dave: He really loves music.
Wade [?]: All right.
Wade [?]: He goes.
Dave: He's not like the other barbarian.
Wade: I've known him a week.
Wade: He seems fine.
Wade [?]: Right.
Wade [?]: He paused.
Kostadis: What's his name?
Kostadis: Pauses and goes, look, as far.
Kostadis: Toblin pauses and goes, look, my friends, I think that whatever plans you might have and whatever adventures you might have and whatever stories you might have, all is forgiven between us.
Kostadis: The past is the past.
Kostadis: The future is the future.
Dave: What are you forgiving me for?
Kostadis: I'm not forgiving you.
Kostadis: I'm forgiving all barbarians.
Kostadis: I'm telling.
Kostadis: I'm talking about.
Dave: The barbarian.
Wade [?]: Yes.
Dave: Oh, yeah.
Wade: He's following a hashtag not all barbarians.
Dave [?]: Yes, not all barbarians.
Dave: Well said.
Kostadis: Right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: And so he's like, but I do recommend you go talk to you if you're looking for work.
Kostadis: Well, if you're looking to spend some money, I don't need a place to stay.
Kostadis: I do have a room.
Gary: Bramgrim.
Gary: I can't afford to live here.
Wade: Yeah, I don't think we've got enough money for all of us.
Kostadis [?]: We'll have to go collect some coin.
Kostadis: Yes, well, in that case, I do recommend you go check the quest board out.
Kostadis [?]: Great.
Wade: All right.
Wade: All roads lead to the quest board.
Wade [?]: We're going to look for the exclamation mark.
Wade [?]: What?
Wade [?]: Look for the exclamation mark.
Wade: The yellow bang.
Gary: The quest board with the yellow exclamation mark above it.
Dave [?]: Yeah, standard MMO.
Gary: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dave: The quest marker?
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: There.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Do they have us?
Kostadis: I guess they don't.
Kostadis: That's really annoying.
Kostadis: They're not doing that.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So as you're walking across the, as you're about to leave, Toblin says, oh, one minor detail.
Kostadis [?]: Go on.
Kostadis: Well, when you're outside, just be careful and aware that we do have a small dragon problem.
Kostadis [?]: The problem with the small or the dragon?
Dave: Do we get paid if we kill the dragon?
Kostadis: I'm told the dragons have hordes.
Dave: People just don't understand.
Wade: Yeah, you guys are all a little too materialistic to robbing from each other.
Wade [?]: All right.
Wade: You know, boiled water is cheap.
Kostadis: Well, why don't you go?
Kostadis: So, all right.
Kostadis: So he says, so do you walk up to the board or do you walk up to the town hall, which is currently boarded up?
Dave: I feel like a board.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis [?]: All right.
Dave: I'm going to go into a boarded uptown hall.
Dave [?]: All right.
Gary: I think that would be suspicious people.
Gary [?]: What?
Gary: I don't know that.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: There are three quests on it.
Kostadis: The first quest is titled Dwarven Excavation Quest.
Wade [?]: Literally named Quest.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Gary: Do we need a tab for quests here?
Dave: We have one under initiative tracking.
Dave: So what I like party inventory.
Dave: What was it called?
Dave: Dwarven What?
Wade [?]: I just put it in the text.
Wade: In the Roll20 chat.
Wade: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: Dwarven Prospectors.
Kostadis: The second quest is the Gnomengarde quest.
Dave: Dwarven Prospectors.
Dave: Talk Gnomes.
Dave: And Umbrage Hill.
Dave: Well, now this is real money.
Dave: You do something, the Townmaster pays you.
Dave: That's fair.
Dave: Wow, 50 GP.
Dave: I haven't had that much money in my whole life.
Dave: A lot.
Gary: Well, I mean, among these options, something that pays more sounds good.
Dave: Oh, definitely.
Dave: Why would we do something that pays less?
Dave: That doesn't make any sense.
Wade [?]: All right.
Kostadis: So which one do you want to go do?
Wade: I don't know.
Wade: I feel like visiting the midwife.
Wade: That's me.
Wade: That is obviously the cheapest one, too.
Wade: I didn't notice that.
Gary: I think I would be leaning towards the gnomes.
Gary: That sounds like the most straightforward, doesn't it?
Dave: Get whatever you can from them.
Dave: If you bring back something useful and don't want to keep it for yourselves, Townmaster Harbin Wester will pay you 50.
Dave: Wait, he's going to participate in this thievery scheme?
Wade: This is a sketchy town.
Dave: No, no.
Dave: The dwarf prospectors.
Wade [?]: That's honest money.
Wade: I mean, so is the midwife visit.
Wade: It's just a little cheaper.
Dave: It just doesn't pay as much.
Dave: Yeah.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: So off you go, I presume.
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave: That okay, Drow?
Dave: Can we do the dwarf prospectors?
Gary [?]: It's fine.
Gary: All right.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Loki, Dookie.
Dave: They've been seeking treasure and relics.
Dave: They're grave robbing?
Dave: What is wrong with this place?
Wade: This is not a place for us.
Kostadis: Good God.
Kostadis: I just want you to know that.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis [?]: At what?
Kostadis: Nothing, nothing.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: No, that we're his favorite group of players.
Kostadis: Yeah, no, I'm just like, you are by far.
Kostadis: Okay, so where are we?
Kostadis: I just need to go back to the.
Kostadis: Okay, so you're on the main map, right?
Wade: Yeah, we're on the Sword Coast or whatever it is.
Wade: Yeah, Sword Coast.
Kostadis: What is the scale of this map?
Wade: One hex is five miles.
Wade [?]: All right, so that's like 15 miles.
Kostadis: That's a day's hike.
Kostadis: So let's go to Icespire Peak.
Wade: Maybe, you know, human speed at my speed, it's like three days.
Kostadis: What is your speed, by the way?
Wade: No, it's actually 30 feet.
Wade: It's pretty standard.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, you're standard.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: It's a little, I mean, it's.
Kostadis: So, okay, so it's not a, you don't have a, there isn't a pet speed penalty.
Wade: It doesn't appear to be.
Wade: I can't wear armor, which is kind of funny, but you know, also unnecessary for a druid.
Kostadis: Yep.
Kostadis: Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Gary: Where is it?
Gary: Can you crap and scavenge food on our way?
Wade: Oh, I mean, I've got proficiency in survival and nature, right?
Wade: Like, I'm sure I could scavenge food with that stuff.
Wade [?]: Yes.
Wade: There you go.
Wade: Something a little better than some goodberries.
Wade: And it might not kill you.
Wade: I don't know about that role.
Gary: It's a little bit.
Wade: But hey, I've got proficiency in nature.
Wade: Oh, no.
Wade: Well, the medicine will also kill you.
Gary: Well, at least we have a good look.
Wade: No, I didn't pick any of the conjure food spells.
Gary: Goodberry should be on a Druid's spell list, right?
Wade: Maybe not at level one, managed spells.
Wade: Let me check.
Gary: Well, it's level one Ranger.
Wade [?]: All right.
Gary: So.
UNKNOWN: Oh, good.
UNKNOWN: Okay, I could prepare Goodberries.
UNKNOWN: There you go.
UNKNOWN: I'll take off, I don't know, Longstrider or something.
Wade: Ice knife, I'm never going to use that.
Wade [?]: The journey.
Kostadis: All right, so I presume you're going normal pace, right?
Kostadis: Do you want to look for food or do you have rations?
Dave: I still have two rations that I haven't eaten.
Dave [?]: All right.
Wade: I'm more of a scavenger, live off the land.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So you arrive uneventfully at the dwarven excavation location.
Wade: Where is that on this?
Wade: It's southeast, like three hexes, was it?
Gary [?]: Yeah, yeah.
Gary [?]: So it's right here.
Wade: That's southwest, even though the quest says southeast.
Kostadis: I get it in the wrong way.
Wade: Oh, sorry, that's Dwarven Prospectors, not the Rock Gnomes.
Kostadis [?]: Yes, you're right.
UNKNOWN: I'm reading the wrong one.
Kostadis [?]: Ignore me.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okie dokie.
Kostadis [?]: Nothing crazy on the way.
Dave: There's no charge around here.
Dave [?]: Well done.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Wade: Oh, this is literally just delivering a letter.
Wade: All right.
Wade [?]: It's a fetch quest.
Wade: Well, reverse.
Wade: It's deliver.
Dave: For the moment.
Wade: Oh, yeah.
Wade: Nothing ever changes on the quest.
Wade: It's set in stone.
Dave [?]: Exactly.
Dave: Especially when we change the quest.
Wade: Well, we just do that to troll the GM.
Wade [?]: Totally.
Kostadis: Are you trying to say something?
Wade [?]: All right.
Kostadis: All right.
Wade: Trying.
Wade: Yes.
Wade: C is an Echo 1 for what it's worth.
Dave: Yeah.
Kostadis: Do you guys see your characters?
Dave [?]: No, I just see Echo One.
Dave: You see black and then E1.
Kostadis: Ah, why do they not do this?
Wade [?]: Do you see something?
Wade: I still just see Echo 1.
Kostadis: Can you reload?
Gary [?]: Sure.
Wade: Consulting ancient texts.
Wade: Crafting spells.
Wade: Nope.
Wade: Still just Echo 1.
Dave: No change.
Gary: There's pineapple on the pizza then.
Wade: Was that per us?
Kostadis: You should see something now.
Kostadis [?]: Nope.
Dave: Nope.
Kostadis: It's like.
Kostadis [?]: Nope.
Kostadis: What would you, what are like we see a little circle?
Wade: And we're reloading again.
Wade: Hold on.
Dave: Nope.
Wade [?]: Nope.
Wade [?]: Ah, that makes part of the problem.
Dave [?]: Okay, now I see something.
Wade: Excellent.
Wade: I can still see E1, but I can see the camera.
Dave [?]: We're going into the mine.
Dave: I see.
Wade [?]: Yeah, hold on.
Wade [?]: I figured out what the problem was.
Wade: Sorry.
Wade: There's another problem.
Wade: I can't grab my token.
Kostadis: Yes, I know.
Kostadis: That was the problem.
Kostadis [?]: Oh.
Kostadis [?]: Hey, I can grab me now.
Wade [?]: Yes, hold on.
Kostadis: That was why the character sheets were not, they were not showing.
Kostadis: Save changes.
Wade [?]: Bramgrim is fixed.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: I need to just fix the vision on the characters here.
Wade [?]: Yeah, and I can't move the Drow one you're in.
Wade: Yeah, I agree.
Wade: I can only hit the other three.
Kostadis: Oh, right.
Kostadis: Okay, the Drow one is the one that you can't see.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So you should now be able to move it, Gary.
Kostadis: Can you?
Kostadis [?]: I can.
UNKNOWN: Yes.
Kostadis: I'm seeing.
Kostadis: Yep.
UNKNOWN: Everybody can.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Kostadis: The canyon's rocky walls rise to the height of 80 feet.
Kostadis: At the end of the canyon, a 20-foot-high wall of black stone has broken the gate carved into it.
Kostadis: has a broken gate carved into it, with one stone door hanging precariously by a hinge, and the other door missing.
Kostadis: Beyond this open gate, in the shadow of a great mountain to the east, lies a ruined settlement.
Kostadis: All is quiet.
Wade [?]: Guys?
Wade: Is there anybody here to deliver the message to?
Kostadis: I just put the description there.
Dave: Great.
Kostadis: So.
Dave: Why is the gate broken?
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: Let me just do something.
Wade: I've heard stories of a white dragon flying around here.
Wade: Perhaps that killed the gate.
Dave: We are not going to get our 50 GP.
UNKNOWN: Jeez.
Wade: No, no.
Wade: All we have to do is go back and say we delivered the message.
Dave: But that would be dishonest.
Wade: Fair.
Dave: Although you do have a point.
Wade: No, no, no.
UNKNOWN: That would be dishonest.
Dave: Yeah.
Wade: We're here to heal the land, not to, you know, be another blight on it.
Wade [?]: All right.
Wade [?]: So do you want to walk in?
Wade [?]: You walk in?
Dave: Yes, let's go straight in.
Wade: Send me in first.
Dave: Yes, no.
Dave: Who's going in?
Dave: Oh, you're going Bramgrim right behind you.
Dave: Absolutely.
Dave [?]: Yes.
Wade: I'm the toughest.
Wade: Also, I got nothing to lose.
Wade: I'm, you know, late in life.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So a partially collapsed 10-foot high wall separates the courtyard from the settlement west of it.
Kostadis: Three heaps.
Kostadis: So are you guys going in?
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So three heaps of rubble are piled high in this area, hewn from the canyon's back wall.
Kostadis: A 30-foot-high temple facade features steps rising to the stone platform.
Kostadis: Facade?
Kostadis: Did I say facade?
Wade: You did.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Gary: So, does it look like it was recently destroyed or a long time ago?
Kostadis: So this is an excavation.
Gary [?]: These are everywhere.
Kostadis: These are archaeologists.
Wade: Grave robbers.
Kostadis: Everybody's a critic.
Wade: What do you like?
Wade: Lawful, super lawful?
Kostadis: No, very confused.
Kostadis: Three feet heaps of rubble are piled high in this area, hewn from the canyon's back wall.
Kostadis: A 30-foot-high temple facade features steps rising to a stone platform.
Kostadis: Cut into this facade is a 10-foot-high open doorway flanked by crumbling, life-sized granite statues of cloaked dwarves.
Kostadis: Evil grins can be seen on their weather-worn faces.
Dave: Is there statues?
Dave: It's dwarves that are excavating a dwarven ruin.
Dave: Is that correct?
Kostadis: Well, as you, do you guys, are you stealthily walking here or are you kind of like having a message?
Wade: I had no intention of being stealthy.
Dave: No, no.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Dave [?]: So, loud.
Dave [?]: It's an excavation.
UNKNOWN: There's bombs and stuff going off, right?
Wade [?]: Very naive.
Dave: We're level one.
Dave [?]: All right.
Kostadis: The two dwarves are very excited.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, sorry.
Kostadis [?]: You said they were statues.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis: No, no, the statues are like.
Wade: Are they these little star things?
Wade [?]: Yeah, those are the star things.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Wade [?]: All right.
Dave: They're very excited.
Dave: Okay, I'll rush up to talk to them.
Dave: I have a high charisma.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: He goes, he's like chewing.
Kostadis: He's like, Dazlin goes, I'll just have you note that this is a private excavation, and everything that we're doing, we're not sharing.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Dave: So we're here from Townmaster Harvin.
Dave: Yes.
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave: And he wanted us to give you a message.
Kostadis: Oh, how kind of him?
Kostadis: What was the message?
Dave: There's a white dragon coming here to kill you.
Wade: Here there be dragons.
Wade [?]: Well, okay, guys.
Wade [?]: We did it.
Dave: Let's go.
Wade: Let's go get our money.
Wade [?]: Yep.
Wade [?]: Right.
Wade [?]: I mean, that's all the quest said.
Dave: I'm walking.
Kostadis: He goes, oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
UNKNOWN: Before you.
Kostadis: Yes?
Dave: Yes.
Kostadis: He goes.
Dave: Did you need something?
Kostadis: He goes, well, you know, do you see the back?
Kostadis: Norbus goes, well, my name is Norbus in Iron Rune, and I'm a Shield Dwarf Prospector.
Kostadis: And Dazlin Greyshard over here is my partner.
Kostadis: And yeah, we've been looking for mountains in the southwest of Phandalin.
Kostadis: And we decided to explore this cabin and we found startling evidence of an ancient dwarven settlement buried by an avalanche.
Dave: Are these your ancestors?
Kostadis: Well, not my ancestors per se, but they are somebody's ancestors.
Dave: Are you working on behalf of their ancestors?
Kostadis: Could Guy just continue?
Kostadis: This is considered.
Kostadis: He pauses and goes, no, no, but it's important to hear the rest of the story.
Kostadis: Now, normally I would be very objected.
Kostadis: I would object terribly to anyone excavating and digging into Dwarven, the Dwarven Dead, but this happens to be an old temple of Abbathor, the evil god of greed.
Gary: Do I know anything about Abbathor?
UNKNOWN: Religion checks here.
Kostadis [?]: Yes.
Kostadis [?]: Anybody do better than that?
Dave: Four.
Gary [?]: I'm not very religious.
Dave: Any more roles, guys.
Dave: Two more.
Dave: Go for it, Gary.
Gary: I said 14.
Dave: Oh, 14.
Dave: Nice.
Gary: Yeah.
Gary: Am I not displaying this properly?
Dave: Nice.
Wade [?]: It's just a story.
Wade [?]: Excuse me.
Kostadis: He goes, well, so you pause, look around, and say, let me see if I can get this straight.
Kostadis: Abbathor, during a solar eclipses, Abbathor is appeased with sacrifices of blood and gemstone.
Kostadis: Dazlin goes, Yes, yes, yes, that's exactly right.
Kostadis: And then you add, and on one occasion, the god found the sacrifices of this temple's priests lacking, so he caused an earthquake, and that avalanche collapsed the parts of the temple and buried the settlement.
Gary: So is Abbathor a god I know from the drow cities?
Kostadis: No, but it's like one of the evil dwarven god of greed.
Kostadis: You know, it's one of those things that I see.
Gary [?]: Okay.
Gary [?]: Right.
Kostadis: You're kind of projecting what an evil drow god would do.
Kostadis: So they're not saying.
Gary: Yeah.
Gary: I mean, like, there's no news here.
Kostadis: It's like, right.
Kostadis: He goes, Dazlin looks at you and goes, yes, but I'll have you note that Dwarven gods are not like your drow gods.
Kostadis [?]: It's fine.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Although Norbus go punches in, she's a cleric of Lathander.
Kostadis: A dwarven cleric of Lathander.
Kostadis: A drow cleric of Lathander.
Dave: It's got unheard of.
Kostadis: There's like, I'm telling you, she's lying.
Kostadis: No, she's that's that.
Kostadis: That's definitely the symbol.
Kostadis: Are you really a cleric of Lathander?
Kostadis [?]: Well, yes.
Wade [?]: Why, indeed.
Wade [?]: He's so gloriously bright.
Dave [?]: Yes.
Dave: Can I cast a light spell on you?
Gary: Yeah.
Room (not at table): Are you going to make coffee?
Kostadis: No, there's a whole other bag of coffee.
Room (not at table): No, but you're going to make it, right?
Room (not at table): Yes, yes.
Room (not at table): Okay.
Room (not at table): Was the child coding?
Room (not at table): Yes.
Room (not at table): Did you tell people the story?
Kostadis: All right, we'll tell it to them in a little bit.
Room (not at table): But I want to hear the story.
Room (not at table): The child was coding.
Kostadis: Oh, yes.
Kostadis: So I come home, and Nick suddenly disappears into his bedroom.
Room (not at table): How did you hear the story?
Kostadis: So Nick disappears into his bedroom.
Wade: For context, I would like to know how old Nick is.
Wade [?]: 14.
Room (not at table): Thank you.
Room (not at table): 15 almost.
Kostadis: Almost 15.
Kostadis: So he walks into his bedroom and he doesn't say anything.
Kostadis: And it's the end of the school day, and I figured that he went and go and play with his computer games or whatever.
Kostadis: He's been quiet for about an hour and a half.
Kostadis: I'm like, okay, I probably should go and tell him that, you know, enough playing with computers.
Kostadis: Does something useful with your life?
Kostadis: I mean, whatever.
Kostadis: I was like, more to the point where if you're going to spend all that, let's go do something together, right?
Kostadis: Let's go get dinner.
Kostadis: Let's let's whatever.
Kostadis: Mom was out.
Kostadis: So he then texts me.
Kostadis: Let me see if I have any text.
Wade [?]: This is going to look great in the AI summary.
Kostadis: It goes, it goes.
Dave: The AI will be very confused by this section.
Kostadis: I did it in all caps.
Kostadis: And I'm like, okay, I guess you defeated some big bat and some monster, right?
Kostadis: That's what my brain's going.
Kostadis: I fixed the bug that I've been trying to fix for the past two hours.
Kostadis: Holy, let's go.
Kostadis: Finally.
Dave: What's he working on?
UNKNOWN: That's funny.
Kostadis: Yeah, he was working on a game and he missed an assignment.
Kostadis: He didn't have an assignment.
Kostadis: And he was very excited because he was finally able to debug the code because it's in Python.
Kostadis: And he printed out.
Kostadis: He was putting printfs everywhere.
Kostadis: And then he said, what if I printf the object?
Kostadis: And the object printed out the values in the object.
Kostadis: He was able to debug it.
Kostadis: So he was very proud of himself.
Wade [?]: Awesome.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: But it was very funny, me like going, I finally did it.
Kostadis: I'm like, okay, I'm going to have to show enthusiasm about you defeating some monster in some game.
Kostadis: All right, I can do this.
Kostadis: I can do it.
Wade: Psyching yourself up.
Kostadis: I can do this.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Room (not at table): I just promised tell Dave that when he says polymorphism, it's beautiful.
Room (not at table): I'm going to tape it for him.
Gary [?]: Oh, my God.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, Jesus.
Kostadis: Oh, Nick did say, I now understand the value of polymorphism.
Kostadis: Did he really?
Room (not at table): He understood the value of classes.
Kostadis: Yes, yes.
Kostadis: Today he understood the value of classes.
Kostadis: He goes, because you could put all the code that's related to each other in the same place.
Dave: Times of programming.
Dave: What a concept.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, to be 14 again.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: You know, there's these moments as a parent where you want to burst their bubble and then you're like, no, no, some things need to be burst in their own time.
Wade: Like Santa.
Kostadis [?]: Leave that for the world to do.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: Santa.
Room (not at table): Santa.
Room (not at table): My dog.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Let's get back.
Kostadis: That's Wade's dog.
Gary [?]: Dog?
Kostadis: That's a dog.
Kostadis: All right.
Room (not at table): But there's a dog.
Kostadis: Yes, I know.
Kostadis: I know.
Room (not at table): Okay, bye.
Room (not at table): Bye, thank you.
Dave: Bye, Sasha.
Dave: Happy birthday.
Kostadis: Happy birthday.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Okay.
Room (not at table): Yes.
Room (not at table): Not yet, but soon.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Soon.
Kostadis: So Dazlin and Norbus, after they have their like five minutes worth of talking, goes, let me say something.
Kostadis: You know, we're just prospectors.
Dave: We're just messengers.
Kostadis: But I agree.
Kostadis: We have a business proposition for you.
Dave: Okay.
Wade: We should at least hear them out.
Wade: Talking is a free action, right?
Kostadis: What about listening?
Kostadis: He goes, I, well, if you were willing to go in there and deal with any nasties and beasties, we would be willing to give you two sending stones.
Wade: Oh, those weren't?
UNKNOWN: Yeah.
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: They're basically like walkie-talkies.
UNKNOWN: Yes.
Kostadis: Okay.
Wade [?]: I mean.
UNKNOWN: Are those valuable?
Kostadis: Well, we also even you would know that magical items are valuable.
Dave: I'm not sure about that.
Gary: We also get the 50 gold pieces.
Gary [?]: What?
Dave: Well, we're already going to get the 50 gold pieces.
Dave: All we have to do is go back to the town and we can get the 50 gold pieces.
Wade: Yeah.
Wade: We just, our job here was to deliver the message.
Wade: The sending stones would allow you to project your music to two ends at one time.
Wade: Just saying.
Gary: So it's Rubir is like, does that mean I can listen to music all the time?
Wade: Well, at the other end of the, you know, the matching stone or whatever has a musician on the other end.
Wade: Yes.
Wade [?]: So.
Dave: Well, maybe we can sell them.
Dave: They're probably worth something.
Wade: Do you have any idea what's in there?
Wade: Asking the dwarves what lies beyond.
Wade: You just said, you know, take care of some nasties and beasties.
Wade: What have you seen?
Dave: So what do you, what do you say more about what you're expecting us to do?
Kostadis [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis: Well, I mean, just go inside and if you see anything that is dangerous, kill it.
Wade: Do we look dangerous?
Kostadis: If you were bad people, yes.
Dave: I just want to be clear.
Dave: All of the treasure, you call it, relics, all of that stuff, you're going to be returning that to the rightful owners, correct?
Dave [?]: Yes, of course.
Dave: Okay, so we'll consider for you.
Wade: Make sure they don't consider themselves the rightful owners.
Dave: Oh.
Dave: That's good, mate.
Wade: How green are you?
Gary: We're level one.
Wade [?]: I mean, come on.
Dave: My whole life studying music and nothing else.
Dave: What do you think?
Wade: You kids, you whipper snappers.
Wade [?]: All right.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So, you don't have to come.
Kostadis: You don't have to do this.
Kostadis: You can come back later to go help them.
Kostadis: There's no requirement to do things in any particular order.
Dave: Right, sure.
Kostadis: Just want to make sure.
Kostadis [?]: I've already made the day's journey.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: So you will go in?
Wade: We may as well have a look around and decide, you know, if it's worth our effort.
Wade [?]: All right.
Dave [?]: Okay.
Kostadis: Can someone put you guys in the right marching order?
Wade: It'll be me up front. Does anybody have a passive perception of 15? No. Not me. Oh, all right. Oh, man. We need a ranger. Let's go with this as the. Wait, passive perception.
Wade: Valfyn has 15.
Wade [?]: Oh, she does?
Gary [?]: Wait, are you kidding me?
Gary: Passive perception 15?
Gary: Yeah.
Gary [?]: Oh, look at it.
Kostadis: It's on the internet.
Gary [?]: I was going to say, wait, how could a character of Gary's not have high perception?
Gary: Well, you know, she's just got high wisdom.
Dave [?]: That helps.
Gary [?]: Yes.
Kostadis: Gary, you're a trope.
Kostadis [?]: Aren't we all?
Kostadis [?]: Like, everybody's a trope of some kind.
Kostadis: Yeah, I know, but Gary's characters always have high perception.
Dave [?]: It's also happening.
Gary [?]: Yeah, because they've been rogues and clerics.
Gary: And rangers, I guess.
Kostadis: Yeah, yeah, rogues with clerics and rangers.
Kostadis: You can't have low perception.
Kostadis: It's just an it's a flute.
Kostadis: That's right.
Kostadis [?]: It's anathema.
Kostadis: So your characters always have high perception.
Room (not at table): They fed the dogs, right?
Kostadis: I believe so, yes.
Room (not at table): They're not.
Kostadis: Yeah, he did feed them.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: You notice a secret door.
Kostadis [?]: Oh, is that the S?
Kostadis: Yes, that is the S.
Wade: Can you tell us about it?
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: Norbus, however, says, well, before you go any deeper, I think it's only fair that we tell you what we did discover.
Kostadis [?]: We did ask.
Kostadis: Yes, yes.
Kostadis: We did see an ochre jelly. Oh, dear. Bad. What? That's not so bad. Yes, it was bad.
Kostadis: I mean, just very dangerous creatures.
Kostadis: We ran out before we could face them.
Gary: Aren't those really bad?
Kostadis: He goes, Norbus goes, look, we are dwarven prospectors and explorers.
Kostadis: I don't know whether what makes a dangerous monster or an easy monster.
Kostadis: You've got swords and you know how to cast spells and you have a buff shell.
Wade: The shell doesn't help me, you know, eliminate the jelly.
Kostadis: Well, I mean, what I'm trying to say is that you seem to me as powerful, worthy adventurers.
Dave: We're all levels.
Wade [?]: Stones are worth a lot of money, guys.
UNKNOWN: Come on.
Wade: Wait, how much?
Dave: I don't know.
Dave: I think we might be able to get like a couple hundred gold pieces for them.
Wade: Well, that would be a big, big update.
Wade: But we need to keep ourselves alive.
Wade: Oh, sure.
Dave: Jelly.
Dave: When your alternative is starving, you're willing to take some risks.
Kostadis: Okay.
Kostadis: So, would you want to go down the secret door or definitely the secret door?
Dave: I've never been through a secret door.
Dave: That sounds cool.
Wade [?]: All right.
Dave: I'll go first.
Wade: Oh, really?
Wade: You'll delete the chart.
Wade: All right.
Dave: Okay.
Dave: C of 13, I'll be fine.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis [?]: You know.
Kostadis: You arrive at a door.
Kostadis [?]: A door.
Kostadis [?]: Is it a secret door?
Kostadis: No, no.
Kostadis: There's a door.
Kostadis: You can see what you should be able to see what you're seeing.
Wade: Regular.
Wade: Yeah, we see a little hallway with like a door here at the end of it, I think.
Kostadis: Yeah, so what do you do?
Kostadis: Go through the door to the north or the door to the west?
Wade [?]: East.
Kostadis: Ah, east, actually.
Kostadis: All right, to through the door to the east.
Wade: We are blacked off.
Kostadis: You are?
Kostadis: I don't see anything past the east door.
UNKNOWN: It's there.
Kostadis: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Kostadis: Let me just.
Kostadis: Hold on, hold on.
Kostadis: There we go.
Kostadis: This is like, this is old school.
Wade: There we go.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: There you go.
Kostadis: Here you go.
Kostadis: Let's see.
Kostadis: And then we'll stop here.
Kostadis: An earthquake collapsed part of this room, which holds nothing of value.
Kostadis: Wow.
Dave: That's where we're stopping.
Dave: Come on.
Dave: I mean, if that's it, then let's go through the other door.
Wade [?]: Yeah.
Wade [?]: Hit the door.
Wade [?]: All right.
Dave [?]: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Nothing at value.
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: I'll go through.
Kostadis: Are you going to go through?
Kostadis: Hold on.
Kostadis: I have to fix the lighting mic.
Kostadis: Yep.
Kostadis: And roll a perception.
Kostadis [?]: I'm assuming anything.
Kostadis [?]: Yes.
Kostadis: Does anybody.
Kostadis: So you reach the end of a hallway and there's a door.
Dave: Valfyn, do you see anything?
Kostadis: Valfyn?
Gary: No, I don't.
Gary [?]: No, no.
Dave: Well, I mean, if you really want me to look, I guess I can look.
UNKNOWN: I'm just not very good at looking for things like that.
Kostadis: All right.
Dave: Like I said, I didn't see anything.
Kostadis: Roll an investigation, rather.
Kostadis [?]: Nope.
Kostadis: Nope.
Kostadis: All right.
Kostadis: You find there's curiously door, but as you're looking for it,
Wade: ochre jellies falls on your heads.
Wade [?]: No.
Dave: Oh, there's a secret door.
Wade: This doesn't seem like a very useful passage.
Wade: It looks like it takes us right back to where we had been.
Kostadis: All right.
Wade [?]: So there's, yes, the passageway leads north that way.
Wade [?]: Okay.
Dave: Odd.
Wade: Yeah, that is a weird, weird layout.
Wade: I wonder what this.
Wade: There must have been something in that earthquake room at some point.
Dave [?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: Did we search in there?
Kostadis: Yes, you did.
Kostadis: There was nothing of any value.
Dave: Nothing of value.
Kostadis [?]: No signs of other exits or anything.
Dave [?]: No, no.
Gary [?]: Weird.
Dave: Did we clear the rubble?
Gary: In the big room, did we?
Gary [?]: No, you have not gone into the big room.
Dave: I've never gone into the big room.
Kostadis: This is the partially collapsed room.
Kostadis: Hold on, let me write it down.
Dave: So if I go back in here, is there can I clear the rubble?
Kostadis: Can you clear the rubble?
Dave: But it's only partially collapsed.
Dave: It's not fully collapsed.
Kostadis: Okay, so you're still dead.
UNKNOWN: It's still alive.
Dave: That's right.
Dave: Slightly alive.
Wade [?]: So let's see.
Wade: You just move the text where we can't read it.
Kostadis: Yeah, I know.
Kostadis: It's like, hold on.
Wade [?]: It's good there.
Wade [?]: It's not in there anyway.
Kostadis: There it is.
Kostadis: No, it was just an it was just annoying me.
Kostadis: All right, okay.
Kostadis: So you're digging in the partially collapsed room.
Kostadis: And so you continue to dig.
Kostadis: But after a certain amount of digging, well, it's possible that things could get disrupted and rolled around.
Kostadis: Do you want to just keep digging, take your chances, or like think about it a little bit more?
Gary: I think we should look around more.
Gary: This seems unproductive.
Wade: I still have architectural questions about this place that make this room very interesting.
Dave: Well, they were mining it and it kind of collapsed while they were mining it.
Wade: Was it a room or a mine shaft?
UNKNOWN: Like, what is it?
UNKNOWN: Like, how furnished is this room or finished, I should say?
Dave: It's just a cave.
Kostadis: No, so remember, this is part of a temple complex.
Kostadis: So who knows what?
Kostadis: So since you asked, and since I can provide, oh, dear.
Kostadis: I reach for the books.
Kostadis: Let's see.
Kostadis: There's usually something I can get here.
Kostadis: Right.
Kostadis: So the wall has several protruding blocks.
Kostadis: As you look at them, they're designed to allow defenders within the chamber to gain cover from one of the chamber's entrances.
Wade: There's only one entrance in the chamber.
Kostadis: Well, yes.
Kostadis [?]: Well, currently.
Kostadis: Yes, currently.
Kostadis: And so, what you gather from the position of these things is that there was an entrance on the other side that this room connects to another part to the northeast, west, east, yes, northeast.
Dave: But it's no longer accessible.
Kostadis: Yes.
Dave: All right.
UNKNOWN: Well, thanks, guys.
Dave [?]: All right.
Gary [?]: Are you going to try to play next week?
Kostadis [?]: We'll try.
Kostadis [?]: Yes.
Kostadis: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Excellent.
Kostadis: Well, that's all we can ask for is to try.
Kostadis [?]: There is no try.
Kostadis: Oh, by the way, Gary, I'm going to tell you something.
Kostadis: Time shifter.
Kostadis: Get the app time shifter.
Gary: Oh, this is for changing time zones.
Kostadis: Yes.
Kostadis: I swear it has been life-changing in my experience over the last two, three years.
Kostadis: It is not, it's not really hokey.
Kostadis: It just tells you when to go to sleep.
Kostadis: And if you want to spend like five days adjusting your time schedule, it works.
UNKNOWN: And if you just want to adjust it the day before, it also does a lot of value.
Kostadis: So I travel a lot to Greece and it has definitely made the travel to Greece and the travel back a lot easier from a time zone perspective.
Dave [?]: Yes.
Kostadis [?]: Okay, great.
Kostadis: So like, and five times I've done it.
Kostadis: So at this point in time, I'm pretty, I'm a pretty satisfied customer.
Gary: Okay.
Kostadis [?]: Thank you.
Kostadis: Okay.
Dave [?]: I strongly recommend.
Dave [?]: Anybody else?
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: To anybody else as well.
UNKNOWN: All right, guys.
Kostadis: But I know Dave can handle time zone shifts because he is.
Dave: I've never done India, though.
Dave: I'm a little bit worried about that one.
Kostadis: It's not, well, if you've done Bulgaria, it's only like three more hours, four more hours.
Dave: Okay.
Kostadis: Right.
Kostadis: So, I mean, you go to Romania, you've been to Romania, right?
Dave: Yes, yes.
Kostadis: Yeah.
Kostadis: So it's not that much worse.
Kostadis: All right, man.
Kostadis: Good night, guys.
Kostadis: Bye.